{
	"data": [
        {
            "question": "We have ___ him to be more careful in everything.",
            "a": "suggested",
            "b": "hoped",
            "c": "proposed",
            "d": "expected",
            "answer": "4",
            "explain": "\n- Expect somebody to do something \n\n",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "2",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will have ___ writing the report by next week.",
            "a": "finished",
            "b": "hoped",
            "c": "expected",
            "d": "promised",
            "answer": "1",
            "explain": "\n- Finish+ Verb_ing \n- Hope/expect/promise+ to Verb",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "2",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was ___ to leave the room, when the phone rang.",
            "a": "just",
            "b": "soon",
            "c": "about",
            "d": "immediately",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "\n- About + To Verb: on the point of doing something; to be ready to do something new",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "2",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "___ with, I have no time to have a date with you.",
            "a": "To begin",
            "b": "Beginning",
            "c": "Begin",
            "d": "To beginning",
            "answer": "1",
            "explain": "\n- We use \"To Verb\" to say the purpose of an action",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "2",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am sorry ___ waiting out of the room for a long time.",
            "a": "to have kept you",
            "b": "having kept you",
            "c": "keeping you",
            "d": "have kept you",
            "answer": "1",
            "explain": "\n- Sorry to do: feeling sad about a situation, and wishing it were different \n- Sorry for doing something: feeling unhappy about something that you have done",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "2",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "His wealth enables him ___ to England.",
            "a": "to have gone",
            "b": "to be going",
            "c": "to go",
            "d": "went",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "\n- Enable somebody to do something \n- Tense: simple present",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "2",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "She makes it a rule ___ early in the morning.",
            "a": "get up",
            "b": "to get up",
            "c": "to be getting up",
            "d": "got up",
            "answer": "2",
            "explain": "\n- Make it a rule to do something: to always try to do something",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "2",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Too much drinking will lead him ___ himself.",
            "a": "ruining",
            "b": "to ruin",
            "c": "to have ruined",
            "d": "to be ruined",
            "answer": "2",
            "explain": "- To lead somebody to do something = to cause somebody to do something",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "2",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "This apron has no pocket ___.",
            "a": "to put things",
            "b": "to be things put",
            "c": "putting things in",
            "d": "to put things in",
            "answer": "4",
            "explain": "\n- Have /find + somebody/ time/money/ place/ energy/ chance/opportunity/ encourage... + to verb \n- To put things in = to put things in the pocket",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "2",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wanted you to help me ___ my assignment after school.",
            "a": "finish",
            "b": "to be finished",
            "c": "to be finishing",
            "d": "finished",
            "answer": "1",
            "explain": "\n- Help somebody (to) do something",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "2",
            "type": "1"
        }
    ]
}